{
  "name": "",
  "isFavorite": false,
  "cards": [
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Bread",
      "back": "Ekmek"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Cheese",
      "back": "Peynir"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Butter",
      "back": "Tereyağı"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Egg",
      "back": "Yumurta"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Milk",
      "back": "Süt"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Tea",
      "back": "Çay"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Coffee",
      "back": "Kahve"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Juice",
      "back": "Meyve suyu"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Water",
      "back": "Su"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Soup",
      "back": "Çorba"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Rice",
      "back": "Pirinç"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Pasta",
      "back": "Makarna"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Meat",
      "back": "Et"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Chicken",
      "back": "Tavuk"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Fish",
      "back": "Balık"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Sausage",
      "back": "Sosis"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Salad",
      "back": "Salata"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Sandwich",
      "back": "Sandviç"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Hamburger",
      "back": "Hamburger"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Pizza",
      "back": "Pizza"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Cake",
      "back": "Pasta"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Cookie",
      "back": "Kurabiye"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Chocolate",
      "back": "Çikolata"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Ice cream",
      "back": "Dondurma"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Honey",
      "back": "Bal"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Jam",
      "back": "Reçel"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Sugar",
      "back": "Şeker"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Salt",
      "back": "Tuz"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Pepper",
      "back": "Karabiber"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Oil",
      "back": "Yağ"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Flour",
      "back": "Un"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Yogurt",
      "back": "Yoğurt"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Kebab",
      "back": "Kebap"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Steak",
      "back": "Biftek"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Noodles",
      "back": "Erişte"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Corn",
      "back": "Mısır"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Beans",
      "back": "Fasulye"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Lentils",
      "back": "Mercimek"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Mushroom",
      "back": "Mantar"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Peanut",
      "back": "Yer fıstığı"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Walnut",
      "back": "Ceviz"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Hazelnut",
      "back": "Fındık"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Almond",
      "back": "Badem"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Olive",
      "back": "Zeytin"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Pickle",
      "back": "Turşu"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Vinegar",
      "back": "Sirke"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Ketchup",
      "back": "Ketçap"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Mustard",
      "back": "Hardal"
    }
  ]
}
